I'm going to show you how to make Hawaiian pork with braised cabbage and pineapple tomato skewers.
Now I'm going to show you the pieces of equipment that you'll need to make Hawaiian pork as well as the braise to sweet and sour cabbage and the pineapple skewers.
We need a big a large stainless steel casserole dish.
This is going to be used for the top of the stove.
It can go inside the stove too but we're not going to need to do that in this case, has a nice lid to it, a sharp chefs knife.
I have a variety of pairing knifes because there is a quite a few of vegetables in this dish so we're going to have to prep those.
I have a whisk cause we're going to whisk in brown sugar and spices into the sauce that we're going to make, a pair of tongs of course.
Then I have a pineapple knife to slice the pineapple.
I got this at the Dull Plantation in Hawaii and it's great for slicing pineapple and skinning pineapple as well as for other things like great fruit segments and things like that.
I also have another pot with a lid and this is to braise our sweet and sour cabbage.
I'm also going to use some nice bamboo skewers when we grill our delicious pineapple tomato skewers.
Join me when we come back and I'm going to show you the ingredients you need to make Hawaiian pork.